Register of the Stanley Kuhl Hornbeck papers, 1900-1966
Hoover Institution Archives
- Subject and Correspondence File, 1842-1966 (Boxes 1-452)
  - Washington Conference (Box 434)
    - Questions and problems for consideration for agenda, outline
    - Reinsch, "China the Key"
    - Reports
    - Russia
    - Semienoff controversy
    - Shantung
    - Shantung, E. T. Williams' account of
    - Status of Treaties in 1924
    - Swedish View, A
    - Summary of the conference
    - T. F. M.
    - Treaties, 1921-1922; 9.0 folders) (Box 438)
    - Treaty provisions for Far East and Pacific
    - Treaties, ratification
    - Treaties, summary
    - Treaties, text
    - Wilfley memo
    - Wright, Q.
    - Wu Ting-Fang Program
  - Washington, George, 2.0 folders)
  - Washington's Farewell Address
  - Washington Institute of Foreign Affairs, 1965
  - Washington International Club, 1935 October 6
  - Washington Peace Center
  - Washington Post, 3.0 folders)
  - Washington Tuberculosis Association
  - Watches and glasses
  - Waterbury, Clair C.
  - Waterman, Charles W.
  - Watson, Thomas J.
  - Wattawa, John
  - Watts, Prof. James F., Jr.
  - Waung, Ang-chung
  - Wavell, Archibald P.
  - Waveren, A. G. van
  - Way, S. G.
  - Wayne Art Center
  - Wayne Tank and Pump Co.
  - Weapons (Box 439)
  - Webber, LeRoy
  - Weber, Ford R.
  - Webster, Charles K.
  - Wedemeyer, A. C.
  - Week in China
  - Weggelaar, G. C.
  - Wehle, Louis B.
  - Wei, Henry
  - Wei, W. P.
  - Wei, Ken-shen, Dr.
  - Weil, Thomas
  - Weiss, Prof. Stuart L.
  - Welfare state
  - Weller, George
  - Welles, Sumner
  - Welles, Sumner, 1939-1943 (Box 440)
  - Wellesley, 1950
  - Welling, Mrs. John P.
  - Wells, Carveth
  - Wells Fargo Express Company
  - Wells, Marion
  - Wen, Shih Tsin
  - Wen-Kan, Lo
  - Wendell Willkie Award
  - Wensink, Irwin H.
  - Wentcher, Lt. Comdr. Ernest C.
  - West, George L., Jr.
  - West, Henry L.
  - West, "How the West Was Won," Life, 1959
  - West, Major
  - West New Guinea
  - West Point (2 folders) (Box 441)
  - West Point, SCUSA, 2.0 folders)
  - Westchester Bond and Mortgage Co.
  - Westchester County Small Estate Corp.
  - Westermann, W. L.
  - Western Hemisphere
  - Western Union Telegraph Company
  - Western World
  - Weymouth, Anthony
  - Whaley-Eaton Service
  - Whaling, H. B.
  - Wharton, G. W.
  - Wheare, Prof. K. C.
  - Wheeler, Burton K.
  - Wheeler, W. Reginald
  - Wheeler, Rex (Shanghai Tiffin Club), 1955
  - Wheeler-Bennett, John W.
  - White, Arthur
  - White Book, 3.0 folders)
    See also: Judd, remarks on
  - White, Byron R.
  - White, Francis
  - White House (3 folders) (Box 442)
  - White, J. C.
  - White Oak Cotton Co.
  - White, T. C.
  - White, William Allen, 2.0 folders)
  - Whitefield (Opprobrious Octobrius)
  - Whitehurst, F. W.
  - Whitmore, Col. Eugene
  - Whittam, William
  - Whittier, Harriet
  - Who's Important in Government
  - Why We Fight
  - Whyli, A. F.
  - Whyte, Sir Francis
  - Wickersham, William F.
  - Wiesenberger, Arthur, "The Next 100 Points,", 1954
  - Wiggins, Porter P.
  - Wigglesworth, Richard B.
  - Wijner, H. P.
  - Wilbur, Allen S. (See: Vinacke)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman
  - Wilcox, Rev. Edward Barclay, 2.0 folders)
  - Wilcox, Francis G. (Senate Committee on Foreign Relations)
  - Wilcox, Francis O.
  - Wilcox, Wendell G., 2.0 folders)
  - Wilcox (Wendell) Salt Producers, 1948-1953; 3.0 folders)
  - Wilder, Hon. Amos P. (Box 443)
  - Wile, Frederic William
  - Wiley, Charles F., 2.0 folders)
  - Wiley, John C.
  - Wilfley, Judge Lebbeus R.
  - Wilgus, J. A.
  - Wilhelmina Case
  - Wilhelmina, Queen and Princess, circa 1961
  - Wilkerson, Catherine H.
  - Wilkins, Johan
  - Wilkinson, Edward
  - Wilkinson, Theodore
  - Willard, Winifred
  - Willert, Arthur
  - William and Mary, College of
  - William, Dr. Maurice
  - Williams, Burt
  - Williams, Major Clark
  - Williams, Daniel R.
  - Williams, E. T., 2.0 folders)
  - Williams, Mrs. E. T.
  - Williams, Frank S.
  - Williams, James Bradley, Jr.
  - Williams, John H., 2.0 folders)
  - Williams, Margaret Hicks (Mrs. James Bradley Williams), 2.0 folders)
  - Williams, Olive
  - Williams, Roger H.
  - Williams, Wayne C., 2.0 folders)
  - Williamson, S. H.
  - Williamstown Institute of Politics (Box 444)
    - 1927-1933
    - Conference summary
    - Directory, 1923
    - Hornbeck at, 2.0 folders)
    - MacMurray, 1924
    - Round Table, 1927
    - Round Table Conference
    - Hornbeck's Report at Round Table of Round Tables, 1922
  - Willis, Daisy and Violet (Box 445)
  - Willis, Frances E.
  - Willis, H. Parker
  - Willis, Lina
  - Willis, M.
  - Willis, Robert (and the Edwards and the Anguses)
  - Willkie, Wendell
  - Willoughby, Mrs. Westel Robinson
  - Willoughby, W. W.
  - Willys Overland Automobile Agency
  - Wilson, Mrs. Charles
  - Wilson, Edwin C.
  - Wilson, George Grafton, 2.0 folders)
  - Wilson, Hugh R.
  - Wilson, Louis N.
  - Wilson, Thomas W.
  - Wilson, Woodrow, 3.0 folders)
  - Wimsatt, Genevieve
  - Winant, Frederick
  - Winant, John (Ambassador), 2.0 folders)
  - Wines
  - Wingo, James G.
  - Winslow, Alan Francis
  - Winslow, Stewart
  - Winston, A. P.
  - Winston, James Horner, 3.0 folders)
  - Winter, Thomas G.
  - Wisconsin (2 folders) (Box 446)
  - Wisconsin Alumni Association
  - Wisconsin Bankers Association, 1949
  - Wisconsin in China, 2.0 folders)
  - Wisconsin, the Lafollettes (Philip, Robert M., and Robert M., Jr. and Bronson)
  - Wisconsin Legislative Reference Library
  - Wisconsin, University of, 1960-1966
  - Wisconsin, University of, the Badger, 1929
  - Withdrawal of Americans from Far East, 1937-1941
  - Wittfogel, Karl A.
  - Wohl, Paul
  - Wohlstetter, Roberta
  - Women's City Club of Boston
  - Women's Patriotic Conference (Mrs. Griswold and Mrs. Good)
  - Wong, T. T.
  - Wood, Dr. Edith Elmer
  - Wood, Junius B.
  - Woodhead, J. G. W.
  - Woodland Cemetery, Riverside Cemetery
  - Woods, James H.
  - Woodward, Clark H.
  - Woolley, Martha K.
  - Wooton, Paul
  - Worcester Economic Club
  - Words
  - Working Security Committee
  - World
  - World Acquaintance Travel
  - World Friendship Association
  - World Federation
  - World government, 2.0 folders)
  - World Peace Conference, plans for (Box 447)
  - World Peace Foundation
    - General, 2.0 folders)
    - Myers, Denys P. and Rich, Raymond
    - The United States and the Far East
  - World state
  - World War I and II
  - World War II
  - World War III
  - World Youth Crusade for Freedom, 1966
  - World's Fair, Chicago, 1933
  - World's Fair, 1964
  - Worts, Laura
  - "Wounded, The," "Women and War"
  - Wrangel Island
  - Wren, Fran G.
  - Wright, Hamilton, Mrs.
  - Wright, Herbert
  - Wright, Quincy (Box 448)
  - Wriston, Henry M.
  - Writers
  - Wu, C. C.
  - Wu, C. L., 1961-1965
  - Wu, K. C.
  - Wu, K. C., on "Formosa"
  - Wu, Nan-Ju
  - Wunderlich, Lucile
  - Wyatt, Wilson W.
  - Wylie, F. J.
  - Wylie, Lady
  - Wynen, Miss van
  - Wynne, E. C., 3.0 folders)
  - Wynne, Frank B.
  - Wyoming, press release, 1949
    Special to The New York Times.
  - Wyoming, University of, McGee, 1949-1950
  - Wysor, R. J.
  - Yale, Harvard, Princeton Conference, 1938 April 22-23 (Box 449)
  - Yale - in - China
  - Yale Review, 1951
  - Yale University
  - Yalta, 2.0 folders)
  - Yalta, Crimea Conference, 1945 February 4-11
  - Yang, Y. C.
  - Yap, Dr. Diosdado M.
  - Yap, "U.S. - Japan Treaty, February 11, 1922"
  - Yardley, Herbert O.
  - Yarnell, Admiral Harry E., 5.0 folders)
  - Yeh, George (Box 450)
    - Alabama, 1959 October 22; 4.0 folders)
    - Cosmos Club and other correspondence
    - Address
    - Memo, 1958
  - Yen, E. T.
  - Yen, Hawkling L.
  - Yen, James, 1948
  - Yen, James, "Mass Education"
  - Yen, Jimmy
  - Yen, W. W.
  - Yenching Alumni Association
  - Yoshida, Shigeru
  - Yoshida, re Hull's, 1955 November 26
  - Yost, Charles W.
  - Young, Allyn A.
  - Young, Arthur N., 2.0 folders)
  - Young, Arthur N. (Box 451)
  - Young, Arthur N., memoirs, 3.0 folders)
  - Young, C. Walter, 2.0 folders)
  - Young, James, 2.0 folders)
  - Young, John Parke
  - Young, Philip
  - Young, S. S.
  - Young Americans for Freedom, 1962
  - Youth for the Voluntary Prayer Amendment, 1966 (Box 452)
  - Youth Hostels, American
  - Yu, General Ta-Wei
  - Yui, Stewart E. S.
  - Yugoslavia
  - Zablocki Committee, Hearings, U.S., China, E. Asia, 1966 March 8
  - Zaldivar, Josee de
  - Zook, George F.
  - Zorghvliet, re purchase of, conversation with Lieftinck
  - Zucker, A. E.
  - Zumwalt, James G.
  - Zuylen, J. J. L. van
- Chronological Day File, 1931-1946, 1959-1966 (Boxes 453-477)
  Carbon copies of letters and memoranda sent by Stanley K. Hornbeck, arranged chronologically.
  - 1931 September - 1933 December (Box 453)
  - 1934 January - 1935 April (Box 454)
  - 1935 May - 1936 November (Box 455)
  - 1936 December - 1937 September (Box 456)
  - 1937 October - 1938 March (Box 457)
  - 1938 April - December (Box 458)
  - 1939 January - August (Box 459)
  - 1939 September - 1940 April (Box 460)
  - 1940 May - December (Box 461)
  - 1941 January - June (Box 462)
  - 1941 July - October (Box 463)
  - 1941 November - 1942 February (Box 464)
  - 1942 March - August 1942 (Box 465)
  - 1942 September - 1943 January (Box 466)
  - 1943 February - July (Box 467)
  - 1943 August - 1944 February (Box 468)
  - 1944 March - July (Box 469)
  - 1944 August - November (Box 470)
  - 1944 November - 1946 October (Box 471)
  - 1959 - 1961 June (Box 472)
  - 1961 July - 1962 August (Box 473)
  - 1962 September - 1963 August (Box 474)
  - 1963 September - 1964 September (Box 475)
  - 1964 October - 1965 September (Box 476)
  - 1965 October - 1966 October (Box 477)
- Speeches and Writings, 1904-1960 (Boxes 478-495)
  Speeches, lectures, articles, outlines, bibliographies, and clippings, arranged alphabetically by title or subject. See also: Miscellany Box 587
  - "After-dinner Speaking," Shanghai, circa 1911 (Box 478)
  - Agreements and Commitments, Anti-Open Door, 1921-1922
    See also: Washington Conference, Agreements and Commitments Anti-Open Door
  - "Alliances and Balances of Power,", 1914
  - "America's Chinese Policy Analyzed," The Independent, 1927 April
  - American Constitution, The, 1912
  - "American Japanese Relations - Problem of Contact,", 1924
  - "American in the Orient,", 1911
  - "American Policy and Action in Relation to China," by S. K. Hornbeck, Williamstown, 1930
  - "American Policy and the Chinese-Russian Dispute," Williamstown Institute of Politics, 1929 August 27
  - American University, Speech, "The U.S. and China in 3 Ways Divided,", 1950
  - Anglo-Japanese Alliance, 1921
  - Annapolis, 1959
  - Arms and Armament, 1914-1915
  - Army, Translation of the Military Effort of the Allies, Credit, 1931, 1935-1938
  - Army War College, "Foreign Relations and Policy, U.S.," (Box 479)
  - Army War College Lectures, 2.0 folders)
  - Army College, Lectures Delivered at by Hornbeck, Advisor on Political Relations
  - "Bang,", 1917 (Box 480)
  - Beer, George Louis, circa 1920
  - Belgians, deportation, 1916
  - Bibliography of Hornbeck's speeches and writings
  - "British and Americans," Address, Hangchow, 1912 July 4
  - Broadcast to Women of the Netherlands, 1945 May 4
  - "Cause and Occasion of Our Entry into the World War 1917" Philadelphia, 1937 April 16
  - "Causes of the War," Milwaukee Journal, 1914 August 9
  - Chicago Speech, materials for (not given), 1943
  - Chicago Tribune Articles, Japan and China and Japan's Aggressive Policy, 1915
  - China, 1961 June 13
  - China, miscellaneous
  - China, American attitude toward, Dictionary of American History, 1938
  - "China and American Foreign Policy," American Academy, Philadelphia, 1928 May 11
  - "China and the Causes for the Conditions There," Ohio Bankers' Association, Columbus, Ohio, 1927 June 17
  - "China and the Foreign Powers Today," The Chinese Students' Monthly, 1925 March
  - "China and the Treaty Powers," Ching Hua College, Tsing Hua, 1926 January 22
  - "China and Unilateral Treaties," Pan Pacific Progress, 1928 July
  - "China and U.S. China Policy," misc. (Box 481)
  - China and U.S. Policy, 1920-1960; 2.0 folders)
  - China, "The Attitude and Policy of the United States Toward China," American Academy, Philadelphia, 1927
  - China, Communist
  - "China," Naval War College, Newport, Rhode Island, 1922-1923 (Box 482)
  - China, "New Monarchy for Old," Review of Reviews, 1916
  - China, "Opium Merchants Versus Chekiang,", 1912
  - China, "The Opium Question,", 1912
  - "China: the Past and Present Policy of the United States," Naval War College, 1927 May 14
  - China, "The Policy of the United States," Current History, 1927 June
  - "China Policy of the U.S. - Past and Present,", 1966
  - China - Present Situation, to Gregory for I.P.R., 1925
  - China, "Principles and Policies in Regard to China," Foreign Affairs, 1922 December
  - "China - the Revolution of 1911,", 1912
  - China, Situation in, Foreign Policy Association, New York, 1927 February 26
  - China, Situation in, China Society of America, 1927
  - China, Situation in, Institute of Pacific Relations, 1927 (Box 483)
  - China Tariff, Washington Conference, 1921
  - "China Today: Political," World Peace Foundation, 1927
  - China, "Tricks that are Vain," Review of Reviews, 1917
  - China, The Truth About, New York Herald Tribune, 1927 July 17
  - China - United States, "Has the United States a China Policy?," Foreign Affairs, 1927 July
  - China - United States, "Has the United States a China Policy?," Congressional Record, 1928 January 24
  - China, What We Face in, New York Herald Tribune, 1927 May 29
  - China, "United States and China in a World Three Ways Divided,", 1950
  - "Chinese Politics and Revolution," Review of Reviews, 1917
  - "The Chinese Situation" and "What Can We Do About China?," Williamstown Institute, 1927
  - Churchill - Graham Dinner Speech, 1922 June 20
  - Cincinnati, S. K. H. Talk, University of Cincinnati, 1949
  - Communism, Viet Nam
  - "Communism at Work in China,", 1958
  - "Conduct of Foreign Relations," League of Republican Women, Washington, D.C., 1930 November 3
  - "Conscription Legislation,", 1917 May 2
  - Contemporary China, Outline of New Chapters
    See also: Ho Ping Song on Contemporary China
  - "Count Caleb Cushing," The New England Quarterly, 1928 January
  - "Defending America's Policy," The Christian Register, 1927
  - "Diplomatic Relations - Severance, Legal and Political Consequences,", 1916-1917
  - Democracy and obligation, 1916
  - "Distance," Beloit College, Beloit, Wisconsin, 1930 June 16
  - "Distance and Discipline," Address at American School, Peking, 1926
  - Doctrine of Specific Cases
  - East Asia, Linebarger, India
  - East Asia, Overseas Chinese
  - Europe versus Asia, 1951
  - The Far East, 1916-1955 (Box 484)
  - "The Far East,", 1920
  - "Far East, American Interests and Policy in,", 1930
  - Far East, Diplomatic Situation, Chinese Students' Monthly, 1915 June
  - Far East - Financial Problems, Georgetown University lecture, 1922
  - Far East - Foreign Trade, 1924
  - The Far East, Naval War College, 1928
  - "The Far East," Outline, Michigan University, 1917
  - The Far East, "The U.S. and the Far East,", 1942
  - Far East, Principles of American Policy in Relation to the Far East, Cause and Cure of War, 1934 January 18
  - Far East, University Club, Washington, 1917
  - The Far East - Working Draft (for Secretary of State and Income Tax)
  - "Far Eastern Policy of the United States,", 1920 (Box 485)
  - Far Eastern Politics, bibliography
  - Foreign Relations, conduct of, School of Politics, Washington, 1930
  - Foreign Service School, lecture at, and letter from Grew, 1926
  - "Forty Centuries Look Down upon You," Madison, Wisconsin, 1915
  - "Germany the Cause of the War,", 1914
  - "Germany and the United States, the Next Step,", 1917 February 2
  - Hangchow, How the Revolution Came, 1912
  - "Has the United States a China Policy?,", 1927-1928
  - "How Much Will You Give?" Commencement Address, University of Colorado, 1932 June 13
  - Hu Shih, in memoriam address, 1962
  - Hundred Years of Peace
  - "Indentured Labor in Virginia,", 1903
  - "India and the War," lecture, 1916 November 15
  - "The Institute of Pacific Relations," Williamstown, 1927
  - International Law
  - International Law in Theory and in Fact, Philosopher's Club, Madison, Wisconsin, 1916
  - International Mind, On the
  - International, National and Individual Responsibilities, Universal Training
  - "International Relations, Institutes of,", 1925
  - International Relations, a chapter in Sweet Briar College, Sweet Briar, Virginia, 1933 April 13
  - "Japan and China," Chicago Daily Journal, 1915 May 5
  - "Japan's Aggressive Policy in China...," Chicago Daily Tribune, 1915 May 7
  - "Japan's Jurisdiction and International Legal Position in Manchuria," miscellaneous (Box 486)
  - "Japan's Monroe Doctrine for Asia"
  - "Japan's Monroe Doctrine for Asia," Chicago, 1915
  - Japan, notes (Box 487)
  - Japan's Twenty-one Demands, 1915
  - "Juvenile Courts,", 1908
  - King-Hall, Western Civilization and Far East book review, 1924
  - "Korea in Perspective," World Affairs, 1953
  - "La Politique des Etats-Unis en Extreme-Orient," La Revue Internationale, 1916
  - Legislation, notes on, 1909
  - "Lectures"
  - "Loyality,", 1917 February 4
  - "Measures and Men,", 1917
  - "Military Training," S. K. Hornbeck on, Madison, Wisconsin, 1917
  - "Monroe Doctrine, Cuba, and President Kennedy's Declaration"
  - "The Near East,", 1920 May 1
  - Notes on Contemporary Problems, circa 1960
  - Open Door Policy, Dictionary of American History, 1938
  - Open Door Policy - Enunciation, British Policy, circa 1914
  - Open Door Policy in China, Washington Conference, 1922
  - Open Door Policy in China, Table of contents (Box 488)
  - Open Door Policy, miscellaneous, 1914
    Includes correspondence with Professor Clark and Reinsch.
  - The Open Door Policy, revised - complete
  - The Open Door Policy, complete, revised, with comments, etc.
  - The Open Door Policy, original (Box 489)
  - The Open Door Policy, set I, parts I-IV
  - The Open Door Policy, part V, "Japan in South Manchuria"
  - The Opium Question, 1912 (Box 490)
  - "Orientation" Address to the Literary Society of Washington, Oxford, 1963
  - Oxford
  - Oxford, American Boys at, 1905
  - Oxford: The Rhodes Scholar at, Booklover's magazine, 1905 January
  - "Oxford as Acquaintance Ripens,", 1906
  - Pacific, Situation in, 1923 (Box 491)
  - Pacifists, A suggestion to
  - Peace and Security, Chaplains' Association of the Army of the United States, 1938; 2.0 folders)
  - Peace and Security, 1917-1942
  - "Peking Old and New,", 1914
  - Perry Treaty, Perry Day Speech, Bankers' Club, New York, 1934 April 11
  - Philippine Independence, 1921
  - Philippine Independence, Princeton School of Public and International Affairs, 1930
  - Philippines, memos for McCoy and Stimson, 1931
  - Philippines, Observations on, Hangchow Philosophic Club, 1911
  - "Policy and Action in Relation to the Current Situation in the Far East," William and Mary College, 1932 October 18
  - "Policy and Action of the United States in Regard to the Current Sino-Japanese Conflict," Williamstown, 1932 August 18
  - Political Science, introduction to, outline
  - Princeton Conference on Purpose of Armed Force
  - "Principles of the Foreign Policy of the United States,", 1934
    A thesis prepared for and submitted to Chief of Staff, G-2, War Department.
  - "Principles of Foreign Policy of the United States"
  - Public addresses, 1930 (Box 492)
  - Public opinion, newspaper articles
  - "The Russian Revolution and the United States," Milwaukee Journal, 1917
  - "The Russian Revolution,", 1917 April 4
  - The Russo-Japanese Agreement, 1916
  - Sao-Ke Alfred Sze memorial, 1958
  - "Seizure and Search and the Arming of Merchant Vessels"
  - "United States Far Eastern Policy," Shanghai Tiffin Club, New York, 1932 April 27
    See also: United States Policy, Far East
  - Shantung and Kawakami, 1915 April 28
  - Siam, Introduction of Minister, Broadcast, 1930 November 30
  - "Some Activities...Present Administration," Trans-Lux, 1938
  - "Some Principles and Consideration underlying American Policy in Relation to the Current Situation in the Far East,", 1932 April 29
  - South Seas, letters on trip, 1921
  - "Speaking of Donkeys,", 1924
  - Speeches, 1929-1937
  - Speeches, material for
  - Speeches
  - Speeches in Holland
  - "Sun Yat-Sen's Trip North," (Box 493)
  - "Supervised Foreign Travel,", 1924
    See also: Foreign Service
  - Switzerland, 1906-1907
  - Thanksgiving, 1927
  - "Things Men Fight for"
  - "Trade, Concessions, Investments, Conflict and Policy in Far East,", 1917; 2.0 folders)
  - "Twenty Basic Errors in Revisionist Thinking on U.S-China Policy", 2.0 folders)
  - Unfinished writings
  - Union College Address, "Administration of Foreign Affairs," Schenectady, New York, 1929
  - United Nations, Admission of Communist China and Outer Mongolia
  - United Nations, 1956
  - United States Foreign Policy, 1910-1950 (Box 494)
  - "United States: Policy and Action in Regard to the Current Sino-Japanese Conflict,", 1932
    See also: Policy and Action of U.S...
  - The United States in World Markets
  - University of Colorado, Sophomore English essays, 1900-1901
  - University of North Carolina Speech, 1942 May 21
  - Utah State Agricultural College Speech, 1942 June 1
  - War and Arithmetic, 1917
  - "Welcome to the International Student Service Annual Conference," Mount Holyoke College, 1931 August 31
  - "Which Chinese?" S. K. Hornbeck, marked and corrected copy, 1955
  - "Why We Fight"
  - "World Court, Compared with Supreme Court of U.S.," Madison Literary Society, Madison, Wisconsin (Box 495)
  - Writings at Denver University, circa 1904
  - Writings, Madison, Wisconsin, 1914-1917
    Includes articles and press notices.
  - Writings, miscellaneous
  - Writings, 1955
  - Writings, 1956
  - Zimmerman orders, 1919
- Autobiography, 1908-1944, undated (Boxes 496-497)
  Manuscript of Stanley K. Hornbeck's autobiography.
  - 1908 - circa 1912 (Box 496)
  - 1910-1931
  - 1931-1932
    Includes discussion of the Manchuria Crisis.
  - 1933-1937
  - 1937-1940
  - 1941 (Box 497)
  - 1942-1944
  - Undated
- Biographical File, 1904-1960 (Boxes 498-499)
  Articles, sketches and printed matter containing biographical information about Stanley K. Hornbeck.
  - Articles about, 1931 (Box 498)
  - Biography notes, 1952
  - Biographical sketches, articles, photos, etc., 1944-1947
  - Biographical sketches, 1940-1952; 2.0 folders)
  - Biographical magazine articles, 1930-1935
  - "Our Far East Pilot" by Anne Hard, 1928
  - Biographical sketch for Rhodes Scholars Records, 1904, 1922
  - "Historical record questionnaire," Beta Taus Fraternity, 1933
  - Biographical sketches, "Who's Who,", 1944-1947
  - International Who's Who, 1937
  - Memoirs, 1950, 1960 (Box 499)
  - Biography and Who's Who, 1916-1945
  - Biographical material, 1939-1945
  - National Cyclopedia of American Biography, 1928-1937; 3.0 folders)
- Memorabilia, 1929-1965, undated (Boxes 500-504, Box 581)
  Letters of appointment, certificates, commissions, passports, diploma, medals, Bibles, etc. arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Ambassadorship to Netherlands, certificate of appointment (Box 500)
  - Appointments and promotions
  - Appointments to public office
  - Baptismal certificate
  - Beta Theta Pi, Handbook
  - Birth certificate affidavit
  - Birthday and horoscopic data
  - Commissions
  - Description of Hornbeck's publishing activity
  - Hornbeck, Stanley K., 1929-1943
  - Japan (Box 501)
  - Letters of introduction and recommendation
  - Military record
  - Military record of service
  - Newspaper clippings, invitations, programs
  - Passports
  - Trip, Hawaiian Islands, 1935
  - Utrecht, State University of, honorary degree